this video is going to introduce the
该视频将介绍
idea of mixed strategies and explain why
混合策略的想法并解释原因
they're important to Nash equilibria so
它们对纳什均衡很重要，所以
the example that I want to think about
我想想的例子
here is the United Nations setting up
这是联合国的设置
checkpoints to defend against terrorist
防御恐怖分子的检查站
attacks at a port in Somalia and you can
袭击索马里的一个港口，你可以
see that what happens is they they place
看看发生什么事了
a checkpoint on the road they stop all
他们在路上阻止所有的检查站
cars like this taxi here and they go
像这样的出租车在这里的车，他们去
through the contents of the car to make
通过汽车的内容来制作
sure that it doesn't contain any
确保它不包含任何
explosives or other dangerous materials
炸药或其他危险材料
now let's think about this situation as
现在让我们考虑这种情况
a game so there are a variety of
一个游戏，所以有各种各样的
different roads that the UN could choose
联合国可以选择的不同道路
to set up its checkpoint on every hour
每小时设置其检查点
and for each one of those roads the the
对于其中的每条道路，
potential attacker could decide to
潜在的攻击者可以决定
attack that road and if it's the case
攻击那条路，如果是这样
that the defender defended that road and
捍卫者捍卫了这条路，
the attacker attacks it then the
攻击者攻击它，然后
attacker gets a large negative payoff
攻击者获得了巨大的负收益
because they're captured and their
因为他们被捕获了
attack is not successful if on the other
如果对方攻击不成功
hand the attacker attacks any other road
攻击者攻击其他道路
then the attack is successful and then
然后攻击成功，然后
the utility of the attacker depends on
攻击者的效用取决于
the value of the target that was
目标的价值是
attacked and wasn't defended now it's
被攻击，现在没有被捍卫
pretty clear that if the UN were to
很清楚，如果联合国要
commit to any deterministic strategy if
致力于任何确定性策略，如果
they were to choose their action in any
他们将在任何情况下选择自己的行动
deterministic way things are going to go
确定性的方式
pretty badly for them because the
对他们来说非常糟糕，因为
defender asserting the attacker would be
声称攻击者是
able to look at what they're doing then
然后可以看看他们在做什么
they'd be able to watch for a while see
他们可以看一会儿
what strategy the UN is following and
联合国正在采取什么策略？
then attack something different and
然后攻击不同的东西
attacks would always be successful so it
攻击将永远是成功的，所以它
must be that this is not really how
必须是这不是真的
checkpoints get set up and indeed what
建立检查点，实际上是什么
really happens is that the checkpoints
真正发生的是检查站
are set up in a randomized way so that
以随机方式设置，以便
even if the attacker is watched for a
即使攻击者受到监视
while and figure out what the randomized
一会儿，弄清楚什么是随机的
strategy is they're not able to know on
策略是他们不知道
a given hour where the checkpoints are
给定小时内检查点所在的位置
going to be
将
and this means that their value of an
这意味着他们的价值
attack is limited so the Nash
攻击是有限的，所以纳什
equilibrium of a game like this is going
像这样的游戏平衡
to involve the defender defending in a
让辩护人参与
randomized way like this and this kind
像这样的随机方式
of a randomized strategy is called a
的随机策略称为
mixed strategy and that's going to be
混合策略，这将是
the topic of the next sequence of videos
下一段视频的主题